sirlinksalot.net 2007-12-16

# SirLinksalot.net Privacy Policy

**[SirLinksalot.net](http://www.sirlinksalot.net/) Privacy Policy**

**Our privacy policy is detailed below and we ask   you to read it in full.  We also encourage you periodically review this page to be informed as to how we are protecting your privacy.**

**External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. **SirLinksalot.net** and **Walker Marketing, Inc.** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Counted.com**

This website collects statistical information using information provided by Counted.com.  The privacy policy for Counted.com 

can be found [**by clicking here**](http://www.counted.com/information/privacy/).

**Microsoft bCentral**

Selected pages within this website collect email addresses on an opt-in basis for the sole purpose of providing access to information to the user about topics covered by the site. These addresses are used solely for the stated purpose and will not intentionally be sold, exchanged or otherwise revealed by SirLinksalot.net or Walker Marketing, Inc. to third parties.  The privacy policy for the Microsoft bCentral website can be found **[by clicking here](http://www.bcentral.com/help/policy/privacy.asp)**. 

**Sitemeter.com**

This website collects statistical information using information provided by Sitemeter.com.  The privacy policy for Sitemeter.com can be found [**by clicking here**](http://www.sitemeter.com/default.asp?action=privacy).

**Personal Information**

You can use SirLinksalot.net without revealing any personal information.  The majority of our services do not require any form of customer registration.  

**Advertising/Affiliate/Partner Programs**

We require registration for participation in our affiliates, advertising and partnership programs. These services cannot be offered without first receiving certain information, such as your contact details. If you are not willing to provide us with such information you may choose to not participate in these programs.

During your use of our site, we may collect demographic and profile data. This data is used so we may enhance your experience at our site (i.e. showing you content that you may be interested in according to your preferences). We may share this information with selected advertisers and sponsors. If you do not wish demographic or profile information to be shared, then you may opt-out at the time of registration. At no time will information that personally identifies you or enables an advertiser to communicate with you directly be distributed to any third party.

**Coverage**

This policy applies to our URL www.sirlinksalot.net. It does not apply to our partners, advertisers or any other website that may be connected, in any way, with SirLinksalot.net.

**Use of Cookies**

A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to help us provide customizable services. No personal information is stored within the cookie.

You can choose to accept or refuse the cookies that we send to you by changing the settings of your browser.

**Security**

SirLinksalot.net has security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of customer data under our control. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of the data will not occur, we promise to do our best to prevent against any such occurrences.

**Terms of Use**

By using this site, you are agreeing to the conditions of this Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY, DO NOT USE THIS SITE. We reserve the right at our discretion to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Policy at any time. Any changes will be posted on the site. Please check this page periodically for changes.  [Our full terms of service can be found here.](http://www.sirlinksalot.net/tos.html)

**Contact**

Should you have any questions regarding this privacy policy please **[contact us here](mailto:info@sirlinksalot.net)**.

**Back to[SirLinksalot.net](http://www.sirlinksalot.net/)**

Copyright © 2000 - 2005 [Walker Marketing Inc.](http://www.walkermarketinginc.com/) All Rights Reserved
